Previously on Fightland...
Heavyweight Champ of the world...
My not so little brother.
I couldn't have gotten
here without you. you know.
Get his hands!
Calvin...
Why?!
Freeze! Do not move!
You were fucking
Kingsley Marshall's wife.
Boxing is a criminal enterprise.
Always has been. and always will be.
Yeah. I heard about Kingsley.
No one's seen
or heard from him in months.
Maduka Kilroy's just
been released from prison.
is it true he's coming to
work for Marshall Promotions?
Yeah. that's right.
And the operation?
We frame the Albanians.
and a very bloody internal war starts.
One that Kingsley will be forced
out of his hole to stop.
and I'll take it from there.
It was you who hit the warehouse.
What's goin' on here Duke?
Son of a bitch has a recording device.
- You and him working together?
- No! No!
He's not goin' anywhere.
'till I figure out what's goin' on here.
If not? He's dead.
And so are you. Duke.
Let's all just relax...
What're you sayin'. mate?!
What's he fuckin' sayin'?!
- Duke. what's he say in?!
- Jay. shut the fuck up!
Just shut up. Lazaro. listen
to me. put the gun down.
- Just listen to me.
- Why are you here?
Why are you here. Jay?
Gazzer said that
you was actin' odd. right?
Said you were comin' and goin'.
Yeah. he gave me this address
that you wrote down...
All right. all right. all right. all right.
On a magazine. so I followed it.
- How do I know we can trust him?
- We?!
Me and Duke have been best
mates since we were ten. wanker!
Who the fuck are you
to question my loyalty?!
I'm the one holding the gun. pendejo!
Lazaro! Look at me.
Look at me. look at me.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I wouldn't risk that for anyone.
All right?
You have my word.
Your word ain't worth the risk-
Then do us both.
And then you can explain to Amado
why his entire plan died with us.
Otherwise. put the fuckin' gun down
and let's get back to work.
All right.
If they're not together...
who the hell is that?
And what's he doing here?
Zeek and CeCe's cousin...
Simeon.
He must have followed me from the gym.
The hell?
If he's workin' with the cops.
we need to figure out what they know.
Let me try somethin'...
All right. we need to find
out more about Simeon.
Keep his phone. see what comes up.
Van's probably been made.
I'll dispose of it and our compañero here.
But you need to get to the dockyard
and on to the next step.
No. Duke. what does he mean.
"next step?"
Where the fuck
did all this gear come from?
Hey?
Duke?!
This belonged to Kingsley.
Belonged?
Wait. what-you-you stole it?
Are you-are you fuckin' mad?
Look. if Kingsley finds out.
he's gonna come after ya.
Yeah. that's exactly what I want.
I'll get into it all later. but right now.
there's somethin' I got to take care of.
All right. well I'm gonna have
to come with you. aren't I?
You ain't goin' anywhere.
What. you expect me to sit
here and twiddle my thumbs?
No chance.
Besides. 'Livin La Vida Wanker'
over there
just said your van has been made.
So. unless you wanna book an Uber?
I'm your best bet.
So. where the fuck are we going?
Hear the dockyard they ship
from ain't far from here.
A guy named Nadim runs it.
Albanian geezer. is it?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. name rings a bell.
I did some collection work
for his crazy ass son. Lorik.
Well. they run a fleet of stolen
luxury cars every month
inside shipping containers
headed all across Europe.
We're gonna plant the
stolen drugs in one of 'em.
Here. left here.
Fuckin' hell. mate.
Plantin' drugs?
Killin' Simeon. what the fuck?
Why the fuck are you doin' this. Duke?
The attack in Vegas...
it was a hit.
And Kingsley ordered it.
Well. now you're fuckin'
havin' a laugh. ain't ya?
Kingsley loved you and Calvin.
He treated you like sons.
why would he do that?
'Cause he loved his business more.
Yeah. he found out
that I was gonna leave him...
sign with Colman.
Slow down.
Damn. I had no idea.
Right. okay. so-so what is this?
This is-this is revenge or something?
Kingsley took everythin'
from me that night.
My brother...
my championship...
my life.
And now I'm gonna take
everythin' away from him.
Brick by brick.
And then?
I'll kill him.
Fuck's sake Jay.
You can't go up here. it's no entry.
No. no. no. no. it's fine.
I'm gonna go up here
and turn left at the end.
- It'll be quicker.
- Fuck.
Fuck. Jay!
Shit!
All right. pull over. pull over.
All right. cover the stash. quick!
Easy. easy. easy. calm down. calm down.
- Just calm down.
- Okay. Okay.
He's coming.
Ask me to hand you your license.
What?
Okay.
You pulled an illegal move back there.
Do you have your license. please?
Yeah. yeah. of course officer...
you mind handing me my
license. will you Duke?
Yeah.
Shit.
You're Duke Kilroy.
One and only.
Yeah.
What'd you go.
about cruiser weight. yeah?
No?
Yeah man. fighters can always
spot another fighter. innit?
When I was comin' up. I used to...
I used to spar with the officers
in training for the Lafone Cup.
- Right.
- Yeah. yeah.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
You's are some tough brothers. man.
Well...
What the hell are you's doin'
out at this time of night?
We're actually headin'
off to a training session.
ain't we?
He's thinkin' of givin' it another run.
Yep. just-Shh.
Keep that between us though. yeah?
How 'bout a selfie officer?
- Yeah. go on then.
- Yeah. go on. I'll take it.
All right. man.
- Here we go.
- How you doing?
- That's it.
- Yeah. yeah. that's-
All right...
Okay... yeah. lovely.
- Here you go mate.
- Listen-thanks. Thanks.
Yeah bruv. so your secrets safe with me.
But get that brake light fixed.
Okay?
- You's have a good night.
- All right. man.
Fuck. All right. let-we gotta go.
- Let's go. Let's go.
- Yeah.
We need to hurry up man or we're
gonna miss the shipment.
Shit.
Fuck!
Lazaro. we didn't make it...
no. we took a wrong turn.
Yeah. I know we're runnin' out of time.
We'll have to find another Albanian spot
to plant the stash.
Look. bruv we're gonna fix this all right...
You've done enough.
All right. it was a mistake
bringing you along.
Just take me back to the spot.
So. Zeek Marshall.
tell our viewers about your big plans.
In twenty-four hours' time.
we're gonna to turn this
hallowed arena into the
epicenter of UK boxing again.
From the music.
to the lighting. to the food.
A Marshall's Promotions fight
isn't just a fight.
it's an extravaganza.
This is your first event
leading Marshall Promotions.
What does it mean to you to be
bringing your first fight night
to the magnificent York Hall?
A place where legends are made.
It means everything to me.
This is where young Zeek first
fell in love with boxing.
Come there with my dad.
watching fights together...
it's a special part of my youth.
Well Kingsley. he's shown
great faith in you. hasn't he?
He's put you in charge
of the family business.
but the question we all want to know.
where is he?
Is he coming back?
Mind if we take a five-minute break?
- I'm a bit parched.
- Yeah. yeah. sure.
Do you think we can get
Cebella on camera next?
Good luck with that one.
You're lookin' well. you know. Anna.
Has Simeon put the word out
on the street about our stash?
He hasn't shown up this morning.
He ain't been picking up his phone either.
Fuckin' knows how important
this is for me as well.
We do have another issue.
The robbery exposed holes
in our operation.
Our friends in Africa
reached out with concerns
about sending us another shipment.
They won't until those holes are plugged.
- No shipments means no money.
- Mmhmm.
Money we need to run
the boxing business.
And the casino expansion.
Dad couldn't have picked
a better time for his little vanishing act.
It's been six months and
we still haven't heard a word.
You don't think he's-
Dad isn't dead.
You don't know that.
What I know is in business.
if you've killed the King.
you'd want the world to know about it.
No value wearing
a crown in the shadows.
Maybe.
But what if they don't care about that
because this ain't about
business to them. it's personal?
Been looking all morning.
if there's another place
to plant the Marshall stash
on the Albanians and Nadim.
I don't see it yet.
We need to hit the streets.
scour for another spot.
I can't.
It's my first day working
at Marshall Promotions.
Your friend Jay.
if he's gonna be joining us.
know he's your responsibility.
You ain't got to worry about him.
Anyway. I gotta get to work.
and while I'm there.
I'm going to find out
what I can about Simeon.
Okay. I want to know the
minute you find anything.
1-2.1-2.1-2. That's it.
I'm gonna go and get some
clean towels for him.
No. fuck him!
If he don't pay us. we ain't showing up.
And he won't have any ring girls
for his next fight.
Where's Zeek?
Been asking myself the same thing.
My first day. I thought he'd
roll out the red carpet.
Yeah. well. you know Zeek.
His idea of a welcome
is not throwing a chair.
Right.
So Simeon's ghostin' us.
and now Zeek's vanished too...
Fuck!
Why is she so irritated?
Well. we haven't been paid
for the last few events.
And Jasmine's kind of like our
self-appointed union boss.
You don't seem too fussed.
Simeon's always late.
that's just him. but...
it is a bit weird that he's
not picking up his phone though.
Do you know where he is?
No. I ain't seen him.
Anyway...
Yeah.
So...
first day.
I guess I should get you a welcome gift.
I appreciate it. but.
no gifts needed for me.
Even if...
I was the gift?
Get your mind out the gutter. Kilroy.
I'm offering my help with Kareem.
He's fighting at York Hall
tomorrow isn't he?
And what makes you so
confident I need your help?
Well...
You said it yourself. I know boxing.
Yeah. you got potential.
but I'd need to see more of you
before I decide if you're
skilled enough for that.
So you do want to see me again?
Zeek's at York Hall.
We should get down there
before he pisses off.
Yeah...
Hopefully I'll see you at York Hall.
Jay!
Hey. Lorik...
haven't seen you in ages. bruv.
You good?
Piece of shit. what're you doing here?
Just come for a drink. man.
Yeah. I like what
you've done with the place.
All right.
Out please. out. out. ladies. out.
Come on. Hurry up please.
Fam. this is the guy
I was telling you lot about.
The best debt collector in London.
Aye.
tell them your catch phrase.
No Lorik.
they don't wanna
hear my catch phrase. man.
Aye. yeah. We want. we want.
Yeah...
well...
“If you ever need someone
to pay. just hit up Jay!”
I told you guys this fucker is crazy.
I'm having a post-party
at my place tonight.
You should come around. I may
have some more work for you.
- Yeah man. I'll be there. yeah.
- All right. I'll see you later.
Go.
Fuckin' crazy guy... fuck.
And something that's always played
a- a-a-a vital role
in our enjoyment of sport.
is betting.
Sports betting
is a one hundred billion dollar
industry and growing...
Mr. Morton.
Could I have five minutes of your time?
I'd love to discuss with you...
Three hundred seconds?
That's a luxury.
The lift takes twenty six seconds.
- that's how long you got.
- I'm Cebella Marshall.
I've already tried calling you.
Knew there was a reason
I was avoiding you.
Your father's reputation
doesn't exactly scream
above board. does it?
And yours does?
You used offshore
shell companies to outbid
a government-backed deal in Manila.
Made thirty million.
No headlines. no arrests.
That's not judgment.
That's appreciation.
Well. I'm not naïve.
I just think you're the
only person sharp enough
and bold enough to help me
make this happen.
Make what happen?
Vegas in London.
We already have casinos
in London. Miss Marshall.
True.
But unlike in America.
our casinos don't allow
sports betting inside of them.
I'm sure you already know this.
but in January alone.
the casino sports books in Nevada made
seventy-two point six million
dollars in gross gaming revenue.
I want to bring sports books
to casinos in London.
Specifically. my casino.
Well. that's been tried before.
Never got government support.
A lot of vested interest.
Yes. but... if someone were to be
the first to crack the code.
they stand to make...
billions in an untapped market.
Are you interested?
Well. that depends.
It won't be straightforward.
Are you willing to do what it takes?
I'm willing...
to do whatever it takes
to make this happen.
I'll be in touch.
I'm not getting anything from this.
It's just employment records.
He's got a few gaps here and there.
Two year one. a three year one. but...
Let me see it.
These gaps...
someone like Simeon?
They're arrests.
And all of a sudden.
he's wearing a recording device?
Nah.
This ain't just some cop operation.
He's working with the feds.
Fuck.
That means the NCA.
Amado's not gonna be happy
with cops sniffing around.
We need to find Simeon's handler
and find out what they know.
Look. Look. they're comin' out.
Security closing the door...
Should be empty now.
Let's go.
All right. dump the stash there.
Jay...
There's someone here.
Go!
- Where'd he go?
- How should I know.
Where the fuck is he?
- Check the rest of the club.
- Yeah.
Come on. you motherfucker!
Let's play. you and me!
Fuck. This is bad.
That's Nadim's son.
Hate to admit it. but your amigo's right.
No. not necessarily.
All right. here's what we do.
Go get the drugs from the office.
Duke. what are you thinkin'?
We'll leave one of the duffels
behind and burn the rest.
And when Nadim finds his son.
stabbed the fuck up with
Marshall drugs all around him.
he'll call Zeek and Cebella
demanding answers
that they won't have.
And they'll want to know how
their drugs got there in the first place.
And we're gonna make 'em
think it's the Russians.
- Think it'll work?
- I do.
We just need Lorik here to do his part.
Let's give him a proper Russian send-off.
Give me the knife.
Listen. Duke's a
legend. he'd be a massive draw.
Our streaming partners
are over the moon on this
and I'm willing to do a seventy
thirty split on the purse.
Like I told the others
that called before you.
I'm not Duke's manager.
But you are his father.
and if anyone can help him see
how good an opportunity this is.
it's you.
I blast this bitch out
to my twenty million followers.
I bet we could get him fifteen million.
What. quid?
No cap.
People are clamoring to see
The Duke in the ring again.
I just want to give them what they want.
you know what I'm sayin'?
So. you doing deals for me now?
I ain't making shit for you.
The phone rang. I answered it.
Didn't sound like that to me.
I don't care how it sounds to you.
but these people are looking to slide you
fifteen million quid
to knock out some American reality star.
And what if that's not what I want to do?
Y'know. I don't know what
the hell you wanna do Duke.
and I don't care.
But what I do know.
is from where I'm standin'.
you ain't got nothin'.
And that phone's been ringin'
off the hook with offers
to get you back in the ring.
Least you could do is listen.
I don't give a shit about boxing.
I got bigger things to worry about.
Bigger things.
What bigger things?
Look.
if you don't want to box again.
that's your choice.
But you need to find something
that makes you happy.
Langston?
Yes. Mrs. Marshall?
You drove my husband before. correct?
On and off for the past three years.
How was he?
Aye. he always treated me fairly.
No complaints from my end.
Before Kingsley left. did he...
mention where he was going?
Not at all.
I'll be posted outside if you
need further transportation.
Langston?
I. won't be needing any
transportation today.
The rest of the day is yours.
I'm sorry. Mrs. Marshall. but I've been...
instructed not to let you out of my sight.
Langston. when I say you're done...
you're done.
K?
As you wish.
I'll see you in the morning.
Wow.
Hey...
You hire the place out?
Mmhmm.
Nah. nah. nah.
All the kids are at school.
Does anyone bunk anymore?
Maybe this generation
ain't bad breed like us.
True.
Your brother practically lived here.
Remember when they used to make
you wear the bowling shoes?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Calvin would not have it.
Nah. he used to say that people
and their feet
couldn't be trusted here.
Mmhmm.
Listen. he was right.
Man...
Listen...
about the other night. at the gym.
It wasn't what it looked like.
it was just an innocent
conversation. that's all.
Why you think I care. Duke?
You're free to do whatever you want.
How's your dad?
Still miserable.
I don't know. we've just...
picked up where we left off.
You two are as bad as each
other. you know that.
You always took his side. man.
Well he was always nice to me.
So. what're you sayin'?
You gonna play somethin'?
Come...
let me smash you up.
Listen. we're not in the ring. you know.
We're not in the ring.
we're eye to eye. we're equals.
Stop talkin'. Just pick a game.
That's all you got to do.
You really want that smoke?
They couldn't get me off the table
when we used to go Knights remember?
Knights Youth Club.
I used to love that place. man.
Wow.
Okay. here we go.
Has Kingsley got a table
at home or somethin'?
You ever think for a moment that...
maybe Kingsley had something
to do with Calvin in Vegas?
Where's that come from?
Just...
Here we are. repeating ourselves.
What if he found out about us then?
I wouldn't put anything
past that man if he did.
He didn't.
If he did...
I would be gone...
And my brother would still be here.
What are you gonna do
with your life now. Duke?
The ring was always your home.
At least. you were happiest there.
I don't know.
But this is a start.
Being here. me and you...
What are we doing. Duke?
Really?
Making up for lost time.
No. no.
You're an asshole.
You come back after all this time
kicking off feelings I haven't
thought about in years!
Do you know how unfair that is to me?
You think any of this was fair for me?
I had everything I wanted
eight years ago.
And in one moment...
it was all taken away.
But I never stopped loving you.
I stopped. Duke.
I had to.
Because if I didn't...
I couldn't have kept on breathing.
Then why did you come here?
I gotta go.
Hey...
Please...
We can't keep playing games. Duke.
So let me get this straight.
Our load. or part of it
was found with Nadim and them.
Not Nadim...
Lorik.
But Nadim wants to meet.
Bullshit.
He said it was something important.
I don't give two shits what
he wants to talk about!
Shhh... for fuck's sake.
If it's a sprinkle that
was found. then it's a ton.
This all bullshit. you know?
They're tryin' us.
Dad's not around. so they hit us.
Ain't no respect!
Respect is earned.
Nadim's gotta be spanked.
Yeah...
Lorik too.
That's what dad would do
if he was here...
- But he isn't here.
- So?
He taught us both
so we should lean on that.
He would make an example
out of him and you know it.
So what you want to do then bro?
Kill him.
We can't do that.
Why not?
All right.
All right. you tell me the next step.
We send a couple of heads 'round there
to scope out the place.
before we go down.
If it looks sideways.
we make it straight.
Beauty for mine eyes.
Hi Zeek.
- Cebella...
- Joy.
I'm gonna let you two be.
I'll see you later Cece.
You needed something Cebella?
Sounded important.
You almost got someone fired today.
Who?
Langston?
Let me guess.
you didn't like the fact
that I gave him the day off.
I didn't like the fact
he didn't follow instructions.
Cebella. this cannot be a continual thing.
I'm fine with him being my driver.
- but when I say go. he goes.
- No. you don't.
And why the hell do I need
anyone keeping tabs on me?
No one's keeping tabs on you.
Just trying to keep you protected.
What is this really about Cebella?
Why do you hate me so much?
I get having a stepmom
your same age is not easy...
But at some point.
you have to get over it.
Do you really think that's why I hate you?
Then you are dumber than
I give you credit for.
I'm about business...
my own.
You. though. is what we
like to call a leech.
Someone that latches onto something
and sucks it 'till it's dry.
Just like others who have
gotten around my father.
Luckily for him.
he's able to see through them.
but for some reason. not you.
Good ole Joy.
But you don't fool me.
Never have. never will.
The only person you're fooling
is yourself.
because your value isn't within yourself.
it's who you lie on your back for.
You know.
the difference between
a mother and child Cebella.
is that sometimes...
you need to let a child
have a temper tantrum.
Get some things out their system.
Hope you feel better Cece.
Where is Kingsley. Cebella?
Dad...
is where he is.
And Langston stays with you.
That's final.
You don't want me to tell Kingsley?
We clear?
Crystal.
Finn. finish him off!
Come on Kareem!
Keep your work rate up Kareem!
Word on the street is
they got some money
laid out on their guy.
I suggest you keep an eye on them.
By the time their boy gets knocked out.
they'll be too drunk to care.
I ain't worried about them.
Confident fuck.
When we gonna start talkin' business?
I've got more fights lined up. Good ones.
And I want your platform to show them.
You think you're the only
one with fights lined up?
Clearly not. but ain't like me.
You not seein' this shit?!
I got York Hall on lock.
The ticket sales are going crazy.
And when my man wins.
what are you gonna say?
He's gotta win first. right?
That's very true.
Get back-get back to the corner!
Stay or I don't start counting.
Get to your corner!
Back!
One!
Two!
Three!
Get back to the corner now!
Get back!
- Slow count. slow count!
- Fuckin' time!
Four!
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
How you feeling?
Are you feeling all right?
Keep your hands up. yeah?
Okay. breathe.
Let's go. Fight!
All right. Kareem. you're in.
- Sit down. sit down. sit down.
- Arms out. arms out.
Hey. let me talk to him.
Let me talk to him!
Oi. listen. hit him low. twice.
- What?
- Right. trust me.
Why would I do that?
Right. look. I know this
guy's type. all right?
He's a hothead.
Hit him low. he'll do something stupid.
and he'll get disqualified.
All right? You want to win?
Do it. Go.
Low blow! Fuck's sake Ref!
Keep 'em up! Above the belt line!
Fight! Keep going.
No. that's fine. that's above
the waistline. keep boxing!
Ay! Ref! What the fuck was that?
Cheating bastard!
Ref. what the fuck was that?!
He fuckin' headbutted him!
Disqualify him! DQ him!
That's-that's it! Fight's over!
Fight's over! That's it!
Well. you hit the nail on the
head creating a spectacle.
Boxing loves that.
So?
We'll talk.
DU-KE!
Whoo!
Big W's!
That's what I'm talkin' about. boy!
Fuck you say to Kareem?
Spit bucket guys don't normally
give advice like that in corner.
Kareem...
He ain't ready for
a guy like that. Not now.
It could have gone
a hundred more rounds
and he wasn't gonna win.
Only way he was is if
the ref called a DQ.
So I told him how to get one.
Zeek. man. I saw what was going on.
What you talkin' about?
The ref. the count. how you looked.
I ain't green to this mate.
the fix was clearly in.
but it wasn't working.
And your dad had a reputation
for doing this back in the day.
But no one could ever pin
anything on him
because he was precise.
So if you're going to do it.
you need the right people.
to make it happen...
And I can help you.
I didn't know you were a cheat.
What's changed?
Eight years...
it changes a lot.
Look. I don't know what
I got to do to prove it.
If you need me.
I'm here for you.
Zeek Marshall!
Your fighter's a cheatin' bastard.
Here we fuckin' go.
Gents. the fight's over.
Time to make your way to the exit.
No one's fuckin' leavin'
till we get justice for our boy.
- Now. we want a rematch.
- Yeah?
Last time I checked. headbutts
weren't allowed in the ring.
Well your guy started fightin' dirty first.
and now we've lost a lot of money.
Lads. lads. la-it's-look.
it's been a long night.
let's just take this up another time.
No one's fuckin' talkin' to you. murderer.
Hey. get the fuck out of here
before you talk yourself into trouble.
Now. if you want me
to throw you out myself...
I can.
Really?
It's all right. It's all right.
Now get the fuck out
before it gets worse.
Little Zeek brought his killer along.
Pick him up. Tommy.
This ain't over Zeek.
You're just another fuckin' toe rag
tryin' to be king of the hill.
Yeah? Fuck off.
Be seein' you around big boy!
Vonda.
You good?
Yeah.
You saved my ass there.
I owe you one.
You're family.
I'd never let anyone
do anything to you Zeek.
Ever.
I'll buck you at the
gym in the morning. yeah?
Yeah...
Yo. hold up a sec.
I need you to come somewhere with me.
Now.
I'm supposed to be meeting someone...
Duke.
I need some extra backup.
Let's roll.
What the fuck is Duke doin' here?
We'll talk about it later.
You got some explaining to do. Nadim.
Speech of the year if you ask me.
- Why was our pack at your spot?
- Pack...
that's all you're worried about?
Cut the bullshit. Nadim.
- Where's our load?
- You load...
isn't the point of discussion.
I'm sure you both recognize him.
My beautiful son.
Dead!
Right next to your pack!
Looks to me that Lorik
took it upon himself
to rob from us
and got caught by someone.
You tried to make a move.
and it backfired.
Why the fuck would I make a move
and kill my son in the process?
That's for you to know innit?
Either way. give us our shit.
Fuck you!
You want to lose someone
you love to know how it feels?
You threatening me?
I could snap my fingers right now
and all of you would be dead.
Right...
Z...
Nadim. explain to me what's
goin' on from your end.
Fucking Russians.
Son of a bitch Nikolai!
He had it out for us since the beginning.
He did all this.
- I can't just go off a hunch.
- A hunch?!
The Russians cut out the tongue
of those they don't trust!
They always want to send a message.
I'll do my best to find out who did this...
But I can't have you going to
war with the Russians right now.
It's not good for anyone!
We need calm...
and for everyone to get back to work!
I promise.
I'll figure it out.
My son dies.
one of theirs does as well.
Your father. would have no hesitation.
It's either blood...
or war.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-